{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"1.08/5.4",
			"answer":"1.08/5.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.58/9.4",
			"answer":"6.58/9.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"62.4/1.3",
			"answer":"62.4/1.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.37/19",
			"answer":"4.37/19",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"46.2/7.7",
			"answer":"46.2/7.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.96/1.8",
			"answer":"3.96/1.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.408/5.1",
			"answer":"0.408/5.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"550/5.5",
			"answer":"550/5.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"91.3/0.83",
			"answer":"91.3/0.83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.71/5.3",
			"answer":"3.71/5.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}